Apparently, they blew up a high-ranking military man, now Damir Davydov.
Why can't the Russian authorities in Russia protect high-ranking military men?
It's actually a pretty simple question, because there are a lot of
high-ranking military men in Russia.
There are more than a thousand generals, so you can't just assign
guards to everyone.
And again, guards do not guarantee safety.
We remember that General Kirillov was accompanied by an adjutant, but no
guard will help against a mined car or a mined scooter, as
in the case of Kirillov.
Therefore, we see how, after unsuccessful attempts, guards were assigned to Margarita
Simonyan or Vladimir Solovyov.
Apparently, a propagandist of such a top level, from the point of
view of the administration of the President, the political elite, is a
more valuable asset than General Kirillov.
Moreover, there are a lot of generals in Russia.